Hello, there my name is set
I am honored to be was some fabulous people here today...you
introduce yourselves and tell us a little bit about what you do my name's caitlin and
...sitting computer science...of health nice and what about you
...and I'm in my second-year secondary school that's what's so,
is that I for us and be like tenth grade right in the united states so,
here's a question how did you guys get...I for
media was playing on the internet back in the nineties what was it that inspired you to start
cody both of
our father lex in the industry already zip from a very young age
...surrounded by computers and programming and when we were really
...so we had was like mine...school...dtwo?
And, program to run around and you guys are my
...love this and how about you what got you interested in might bite...from...
into programming just because I've always been exposed to it and?
If at school...and I've notice whenever I go to cope clubs I've always been
...to say code clubs there's such a thing in england what are those
light.
And, the...
As states and...normally in primary school they were
that get children...
programming and it secondary school they're doing...information it feels like a code
...somewhere I'd like to go so here's, here's a question what kind of apps.
We've made...cookbook...we use
and it was originally civic just have ago...windows a...we
migrated it to universal up so...run on the phone and...to
...ten soon so people...I still have to learn how to do this
...so maybe you could help me but that's remarkable example
...csharp is hard and it's wonderful that you guys were able to what about you are you doing the same kind of abs
...together or you have your own we might...together but we also have
...the app called and...and crosses program.
Wants to have a good writing a computer so
...soon ai who can play the game against.
I feel dom might be with you guys this is remarkable so here's another question what
are the challenges that you experience while writing these.
We always find it...to get going
when writing programs we find that will get...do not some crosses...saracsit
...good maybe even a month very what do we do...and it'll certainly be we do that and
then falls out and within a week...I love...as a majority of computer
science is...and what you saw it through typing is really fast right, yeah,
what about you what challenges if you experience...outside the challenges of actually having
time to do it being I have lots of homewood right?
Now...school diverse
...homework I spend most of my time hysteria theater and figuring.
Your haired built what are some of the cool things you...it...that you like.
You have to say the whole...you get to see the howard's I gutsy
attend the presentation so I got to see in use...room and how is
...and how they could paths...models through?
Three...and then shared
...putting an actual...model on the table right...
then scaling down and moving around an actual living room and that's really cool because,
you know, since you've already built...universal windows app
...you will...better at making poland's applications and
...I haven't done that what about you build watered...you see I like they've really
...resource platform visual studio...your own...clyde...by...craft
...I would be look it'd be great to actually else...aren't that's
...look I did not do...about might craft until my boss is like keiko look at might
...is like legos on steroids I did not have that when I was a kid it's a
...it's cooler now we can write some code to do our own
...ok so here's another question of on the serious what can we do as a
community of developers to encourage young people to go into program
...you...tufts when...like ensues...code
...all as I seen it...it's very similar scraps but it's
...learn easy-to-use and it comes with its own guides?
you could give...to resources to teachers...athlete they seem to be the
bits...teach it...to have...than...
They'll probably find a lot easier to teach...advice what you
...at the moment...the uk and...
they teach students icy...which is it's usually...to use words that
must be office park how to work...and...interface but this...to
...that completely with computing which is just teaching...code
...out so I think it's gcc the very keen on students fields
programming at least three languages all...thing and that
is very keen on getting out the...introducing and making
...curriculum...like my two-year-old like I
sort of like we gave them a little a little lap of what those types devices
...start swiping around and doing stuff already feels like teaching young people to use
words they already know-how why not start with...ask another question.
The web...technology issues you guys have any opinion on that what
...to encourage women to join in program encoding thank...
Well, the ten-speed fill insight.
Is very dominated already and they just want...that there
...constable and got and what are some things that we can do to make sure women are more
top nothing showing the route the
most powerful women in the industry because from the outset because is mostly
...you...only men...you think...maybe not this
showing that there are women there already and they are doing while and
...difference as well...awesome possum suggestion so just to finish up
what suggestions do you have three young people and women want to get started?
...just give ago he'd find you don't
...or either do well you can't say...didn't try
...a good enforcement time you will do well and you will enjoy it because
...very rewarding thank you so much...you and I agree
...have ago and if...really difficult...from the of it
...I like it thanks so much for spending some time with
us I feel honored to be with you I wish I could start as early as you guys I
would've loved it thanks so much for stopping by thanks for watching and moi.